(Raj:)- How's your burrito?
- Still a little frozen in the middle.
(Raj:)Probably because I didn't read the instructions.
No wrapper's gonna tell me what to do.
Unless his name is Jay Z.
- Is something going on?
- What do you mean?
(Lucy:)Well, you're acting all weird,
and I'm pretty weird...
(Lucy:)...so I think I know what I'm talking about.
(Raj:)I don't know, maybe it's all those
steroids I've been taking.
(Lucy:)I think I'm gonna go. Thank you
for the burrito and the pork rinds...
(Lucy:)...and the 20-minute lecture on why
monster trucks are better than regular trucks.
(Raj:)Wait, wait.
(Raj:)I found your blog
where you wrote about me.
Oh. I just write that for myself.
I didn't think anybody actually read it.
(Raj:)No kidding. You didn't make it easy to find.
I spent hours digging around online.
(Raj:)For the record, you have excellent credit
and your diabetic aunt...
(Raj:)...seems to be adjusting to her new leg
just fine.